gotprint.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Statement

**Updated: May 25, 2018**

## Information about Privacy on GotPrint

GotPrint is committed to protecting your privacy. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting GotPrint.com, you accept that practices that are described in this Privacy Notice. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement only applies to GotPrint; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products, or services. Please read the complete GotPrint privacy statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need personal information or information that allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are registering before: entering a contest, ordering email newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing and/or registering GotPrint products. Personal information collected by GotPrint is often limited to email address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

We may use your personal information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional material and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out from receiving email communications by clicking on the UNSUBCRIBE link provided in the emails we send or through your GotPrint account by unchecking the Receive Promotions option. 

You will automatically be opted-in when creating a new account or during the checkout process. However, you will have the option to opt-out from receiving promotional emails by un-checking the subscription box on the given page. 

For example, if you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase in the "Shop" area of the website, we will request the personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number.

When you buy a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. We keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our website.

GotPrint also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of GotPrint.

GotPrint also collects information about which pages our customers visit within GotPrint.com. This site visitation data is identified only by a unique ID number, and it is never linked with personal information.

**Mobile:** When you download and/or use apps created by Printograph Inc. DBA GotPrint, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, which includes a unique identifier that your device obtains. We may use this information to provide you with location-based and targeted services, including: advertising, search results, and other personalized content. You may turn off your location services if your mobile device allows it. 

## Use of your Personal Information

We use your personal information for the following purposes:  
To ensure our site is relevant to your needs.  
To deliver services, such as newsletters, which you request.  
To alert you of product upgrades, special offers, updated information, and other new services from GotPrint, if you so request.  
To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site, when appropriate. 

We will merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information to provide more relevant content. In some limited-entry sections of GotPrint, with your approval, we will combine site-visitation data with your personal information in order to provide you with personalized content. We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including: packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail, and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies with the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

## Control of your Personal Information

When you register or otherwise give us personal information, GotPrint will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

GotPrint may send out periodic emails informing you of a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. You will not be able to unsubscribe to these mailings as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen.

## Access to your Personal Information

GotPrint will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. If you register at GotPrint.com, you can review and edit your personal information under "My Account." You will be asked to enter your username and password before viewing your personal information. Under "My Account", you can view and edit personal information you have already given to GotPrint. 

## Security of your Personal Information

GotPrint is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

## Protection of Children's Personal Information

GotPrint.com is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

## Use of Cookies 

When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies).These cookies will tell GotPrint if this particular visitor has visited the website before. The cookies are used for the collection of data about website visits. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. These ads may appear on different websites on the Internet. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. You may opt-out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

## Enforcement of this Privacy Policy

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact GotPrint by email.

## Changes to this Statement

GotPrint will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of this page.
